Rebecca Lacer Thornton, CO 80233

720-217-7983

SUMMARY

The skills I've learned as a University of Denver coding student, pair well with my experience working in Quality Assurance. As a team member for a large manufacturing facility. My basic data review skills were used to release finished product, accept or reject raw materials, and many other things. An example of deep dive data review, would be to identify the scope of a cross functional team project, generally to address something like under performing divisional quality metrics, such as consumer complaints.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: *CSS, HTML, JavaScript

Databases: MySQL, MongoDB

Tools: Git and Heroku

PROJECTS

Git Music | https://rlacer.github.io/Git-Music-Now-Project/

This app allows the user to search an artist and play their music samples.

- My roles were the open api and song retrieval as well as managing the github collaboration repository.
- Technologies used were javascript, html & css.

Express.js Note Taker | https://damp-lake-21717.herokuapp.com/

This app allows the user to make daily notes and save them.

- This was a homework assignment with deployment to heroku.
- Technologies used were javascript, html & css.

EXPERIENCE

NRFU Enumerator

Bureau of Census Denver, CO 08//2020-09/2020 (temporary)

Completing census questionnaires for non-respondents. This was an interesting position; you never know what you'll get knocking on someone's front door as a representative of the US Government. I achieved every productivity bonus available to me.

Quality Operations Team Leader

Nestle Purina PetCare Company Denver, CO 01/2018 - 06/2019 Nestle Purina PetCare Company Denver. CO

<u>Data Review</u>: Data Review in support of continuous improvement in the areas of Raw Materials, In Process, Finished Product, Consumer Complaints and many more. Performed root cause analysis to address issues supported by data review.

<u>Sampling Plans</u>: Routine Sampling on Raw Materials, In Process and Finished Product, Hold Product Sampling and Final Disposition

<u>Audits and Document Control</u>: Complete Document Control, Policy and Procedural Compliance, Audit Prep-internal, external, regulatory – both planned and unplanned visits

Regulatory experience dealing with the FDA and ISO 22000 & FSSC 22000, both as a team member and a lead for planned and unplanned visits

Trace and Recall for holds. Quarterly mock trace as part of a cross functional team, as required by policy (experience as lead and team member)

Certification: Preventive Controls Qualified Individual as defined in 21 CFR Part 507

<u>Current Good Manufacturing Practice, Hazard Analysis, and Risk-Based Preventive Controls for Food For Animals</u> (Revised as of April 1, 2017)

<u>Misc</u>: Expense Reporting, payroll review, employee performance evaluations, inventory, chemical control

One of the last procedural implementations led by me, occurred in the finished product and ingredient labs.

There was a newly approved rapid alternative method for testing ingredients and finished product. The new method had the same range of accuracy as standard method. I solicited feedback from all affected individuals and my team was very excited for the change. With corporate support, Denver was the first facility in the division to cutover. The results were amazing. There was overtime reduction and increased team morale. There were additional cost savings due to reduced chemical inventory and laboratory consumables. Internal control points and data recording were streamlined. Hold product had a quicker turnaround and lengthy lab chemical control policies were greatly reduced because many of the chemicals became obsolete.

03/2006 - 01/2018

Nestle Purina PetCare Company Denver, CO Analyst II

I began with Nestle Purina as the 2nd shift finished product lab analyst. I also worked as the ingredient specialist and even when my roles changed, I continued to backup the finished product lab, ingredient lab and packing room. Additional roles included Quality Management Functional Expert for SAP and QA SME for MES Systems. I enjoy receiving and delivering coaching and training. I believe there is always more to learn and more to know.

Lab Tech/Analyst

Evergreen Analytical Lab Wheatridge, CO 02/2002-02/2006

Strong acid digests on soil and water samples, in preparation to be analyzed by mass spectrometer, in my metals prep role. I later moved to wet chem. This department did more "bench testing". Many of the samples came from municipal water treatment facilities and we were the 3rd party lab used to confirm EPA compliance. This was an NELAC Certified environmental lab.

Airport Customer Service Agent

ATA Airlines

Denver, CO

There was a time when air travel required checking in with a person, that was me. I also worked to recover lost luggage and process damage claims. After nine eleven I was an instant security guard.

EDUCATION

University of Denver Full Stack Web Development (02/2021-present)

Front Range Community College, Westminster Colorado Associate of Science, Math Emphasis (1997)

Emily Griffith Opportunity School, Denver, CO Airframe & Power Plant Mechanics Certificate (1991) Basic Electricity & Electronics (1991)